So I'll just create a new window, right?
Let's create a new window.
So, it's obviously going to ask me to open a folder.
So, if I just drag and drop it in, it should work, right?
And then, just close it. Alright.
It'll ask you if you want to grant it permission.
Okay, so it's empty right now.
Because there's nothing in it.
Alright, so now, let's start building within this folder.
So, let's get back to it.
Alright, let's start building inside this folder.
Alright, let's get back to it.
So, what are we going to create here?
Or, let me see... uh...
Alright, let's go with this one.
Let's follow this one.
This one's a bit more comprehensive.
Alright, let's follow along with this.
Let's go ahead and collapse this.
Let's collapse this one.
Let's get this sorted out.
Let's collapse this one too.
Okay, and now let's take a screenshot of this.
And then, we'll place it right here.
So, for this part, I'd actually recommend creating it manually. It's just better that way.
Alright, so the first thing we definitely need to do is talk to the AI.
We need to establish the context.
So, let's start by creating a context folder.
Let's call it 'Project Background'.
So for 'Project Background', I'm going to give it a number.
Because, you see, you can't just drag and drop to sort things in here.
So, what kind of... thing is this for a folder?
like sorting from A to Z, or by creation time, you know?
Alright, so let's start with '01', okay?
This is for the project background.
Let's create a folder.
And then, click right here, okay?
No, don't click here.
Clicking here will create another folder, right inside this one.
I'm going to click on the root directory.
Then, we'll create '02'.
So, once we have the project background in place,
So, the next thing we'll probably need to produce is what we call the PRD.
We'll call it PRD.
Sounds good, right?
Alright, let's move on.
We'll probably need a frontend prototype demo.
Alright, that works too, right?
Alright, so once we have that front-end prototype demo,
And let's add another one: 00-Draft Conversations.
So, why do that?
Because sometimes, I want the draft to be at the very top.
But if you want it at the very bottom,
Then just go ahead and code it yourself.
Whatever, it doesn't matter. Okay.
So, once we have the front-end prototype demo,
I might also need a 04.
So, this is for reference materials, right?
So I can just drop any reference materials I have in here.
And then, moving on down the line...
And that would be '05, Common Templates', right?
I'll just drop some templates in here.
And then, moving on to 06, that's for our common prompts, right?
Alright, so this is my complete file structure.
There's nothing in it.
There's nothing in here, right?
Yep, they're all empty. Good.
Alright, so what's next?
So, I'm going to create a set of rules for this project.
So, we have this 'rules' thing here, right?
See, there's a 'Rules' section.
Let's click on 'New'.
And then, we'll click on 'Project Rules'.
So, for example, what should I call this one?
Uh, so, the first project rule.
This is the first project rule, let's put it right here.
Then, click 'down'... Oh, wait, that's not what it wants, oh.
It needs to be in English.
Alright, I'll just write it then.
First project rules.
Okay, down.
Alright.
See? It automatically created a .cursor folder for me.
and then RTS under the .cursor directory.
So, what if I want to create another RTS?
And then, back over here.
And then, in this spot, there's another rule.
Then, click 'new' again.
And let's add another project directory.
And this one I'm calling 'second'.
And this one will be called...
Right?
Alright, the second project rule.
And then click 'down'.
If you need to modify them individually,
For this one, I'll probably let it auto-recognize.
And then, click 'Save'.
And as for this one, it doesn't really matter what you do with it.
So, we've got it set up now, right?
So, this is for the project rules, right?
Alright, all set.
So, this is a...
Alright, so what's next?
We might also need to initialize it.
For example, I might have some...
So, once the AI opens up this project folder,
I have no idea what this project is about.
I need to let it know what this project is all about.
So, just a quick rundown of what this project is all about.
Alright, so I'm gonna manually create an 'agent.md' file, uh...
.md, lowercase. There we go.
And just like that, it creates one.
This is a general description for this project.
It's not a rule.
But some agents do define it as a rule.
So, for our purposes here, we're going to define it as something called an 'agent'.
a reference material to help understand the project.
Or, you could say, something like a README file.
Alright, let's just define it like this for now.
Alright.
And we've already got one here as well.
So, why do we need a 'cloud.md' file then?
That's because when you're in Cloud Code, Cloud needs to use this file.
Agent.md is what it needs to use.
So, what if I want it to be exactly the same?
So, it's fine for me to just maintain both of them at the same time, right?
Now, if you're going to use Cloud,
If you're not using Cloud,
then you don't need this thing.
just go ahead and delete it.
So just go ahead and delete it.
And further down, there's something called .gitignore.
So, what's this thing for?
You can just leave it out.
So, what if I initialize a Git repository in this project? Okay.
So let's have it help me out here.
to create a Git repository for this project.
OK, so it automatically does this... uh...
to initialize this project.
And it will generate a .gitignore file for me.
Alright, so this is what we've got.
See? It's already there.
It's added a .gitignore file.
Here it comes.
Let's see where it is, uh...
It's not showing up here.
If it's not showing up,
Alright, let's head back here and take a look at my... what's it called...
But it hasn't been committed yet, okay?
I didn't have it add anything here.
So, for this ignore file...
So, once it's created in the root directory...
It will then help me ignore some of the unnecessary stuff.
And here it comes.
And right here, it'll show you.
It will ignore these things in Mac OS.
And it'll also ignore all this stuff.
and stuff like that.
It'll also ignore things like environment keys and all that stuff.
and it'll also ignore things like build dependencies,
build artifacts, and so on and so forth.
The AI will take care of all this for you automatically.
Alright, so with that in place...
And there's one more thing, what is it called?
It's called Cursor.
Ignore.
Cursor...
So, where is this 'ignore' file?
Oh, right, this is a new feature they just rolled out recently.
Let me just search for it.
Ah, here we go.
Right here... yeah, it should be this one.
Right here in this index file.
So, I can go ahead and create it.
So, uh, let's create this ignore file.
So, what's this thing for?
Hey, this is pretty cool.
I can start a draft conversation right here.
There's one called 'test'... let's test this DMD file.
Alright, so now I'm gonna open this up here.
Let me see.
Let me just try dragging it in, will that work?
Doesn't look like it's working.
And it needs to be in this specific syntax.
Let's see... uh... okay, so first, this pound sign here...
So it means... oh, wait, that's not right.
That's not right.
And right here, I was like, hahaha.
Is this my file?
So, how do I get my ignore file to actually ignore it?
Alright, so here's how it works.
The pound sign is for comments.
So, what do you want to ignore?
You'll need to use an asterisk for the pattern matching.
Alright, let's call this one 'test'.
dot ND.
Okay.
So, it shouldn't be able to match this.
And why is that?
Because this thing requires what's called an 'absolute path'.
Or a relative path.
Alright, let's take a look at the zero-zero... huh.
Here we go, here we go, here we go.
Right here, perfect.
Wait, why is it... oh.
He's not even trying.
Let's just have it do it like this.
Let's see if it works just like this.
Oh, this might be a total flop.
Alright, forget it.
Let's not get hung up on it.
There's also a more brute-force method.
Just go ahead and delete this.
Let me show you how it's done.
See? Right now, there's nothing in this spot.
Just go ahead and do this, right.
And add this file to the cursor ignore.
It's alright.
It's just that sometimes, it doesn't quite get what you mean.
It'll handle that for you.
I just blanked on the syntax for a second.
I just figured this out today, this thing.
See, it's already editing it.
Oh, it's already put it in there.
So it just uses this path to put it right in there.
Alright, hey, everyone, did you see that?
It's got a little 'no entry' sign on it.
See that?
See? It's got a 'no entry' symbol on it.
So, what does this prohibition symbol do?
See? When you select it, you can't drag it in anymore.
See? It won't let me drag it in.
Alright, let's try that again.
Let's create a second one.
Okay, this is the second test.
Yeah, hahaha.
Okay, let's drag it... and... it's in, right?
But when I try to drag this thing, it won't drop in.
Why is there a prohibition symbol here?
Why is it blocked?
Because it's been disabled by this thing.
So where is it?
It's in this cursor ignore file.
It's been inserted right here.
Alright, so let's take this thing...
Alright, let's just paste it right here and save.
And just wait a sec... yep, that one's gone too.
Alright, let's try dragging this one away again.
And then, try dragging it over again.
And on the second try, it won't drag in either.
Got it?
If you got that, drop a '1' in the comments.
So this is a new feature that Cursor recently added.
It's a really useful tool.
The thing is, some of the context is just garbage.
It's just garbage information.
I don't want the AI to process it.
to process it.
So I'll just ignore it.
So, how do we actually ignore it?
So, we're just going to have it initialize one.
So, where is this library?
Initialize it to get into the settings.
Click to search for 'ignore'.
And then, we need to find this thing... what's it called?
So, the ignore file is right here.
Here, you can use path patterns to match files.
Or, you can just do it directly in the settings.
So, right here in the 'indexing' section.
And here, it's a beta.
Oh, right, it's a...
And right here, it has this thing.
Then you just click 'Edit'.
And it will automatically create a file just like this one.
Or, you can just have the AI create it for you.
Alright, so once that's created...
So, which file or folder do you want to ignore?
and just paste it right in.
Save it.
The entire folder gets ignored.
See that?
This thing doesn't have anti-gravity.
He's so bad at this.
You're expecting him to have it? No way, he's not gonna have that.
But I'm gonna need it later!
You deleted it.
But what if I need it later?
But I can still see it right here.
I just don't want the AI to try and understand it.
to process it.
So, I'm going to ignore it.
This isn't what I'd call junk information.
It's information that would interfere with the context.
So first, I'm going to block it.
Got it?
I'm not actually deleting it.
So, there's a fundamental difference here.
So, everyone needs to be careful about what you don't feed into the AI.
Don't let the AI try to understand it.
Alright, let's add this to the context.
Alright, so that's it for this part.
Alright, we have one last folder to create.
This one is called 'agent'.
Right, this one.
Alright, so let's head back to this directory.
Wait, did I close it?
I did close it.
Alright, so I'll just come over here and randomly select a file.
Right-click and open it in Finder, right?
Alright, so now I've got the Finder open.
Alright, let's go back here.
OK, let's delete this.
And then, let's open up our anti-gravity project.
Let's minimize and close this.
Then, let's open a new window.
Alright, let's minimize that.
Okay, same thing, just drag and drop it in here.
Okay, so now the anti-gravity feature is on.
So, should we just trust this folder?
Alright, let's click on this option called 'Custom'.
And then, right here, we're gonna add something called... what should we call it?
So, 'NT'.
Right?
Integrity.
And then, RULES.
Alright, pay attention. See how this spot is empty right now? Let's save it.
See? It's added an 'agents' folder.
And then, the 'rules' folder gets placed right in here.
See that?
And this is me, hahaha.
Alright, so these are the rules inside the 'anti-gravity' folder.
So it's been placed right here.
Alright, so let's head back to the folder we were just in.
So now, this is what we've created.
Alright, so this is what we've created so far.
Alright.
Alright, let's head back here.
Alright, let's get back to it and follow along.
See, the 'Project Background' is our context.
Alright, we've created it.
The reference template is right here, uh...
This reference template is just a commonly used one.
Then, the front-end demo is here, along with the reference materials.
And here are the commonly used prompts.
So, agent.md. Got it?
So, it's basically a general description for the entire project.
This helps the AI understand what this project is all about.
And the cloud.md file? That's for Cloud.
It's pretty slick.
It forces you to create one.
Alright, so this one here, the .gitignore...
It's used to ignore files that don't need to be added to Git.
certain tracked files.
And then there's the cursor.ignore, which is for the Cursor IDE.
It needs to exclude some files that are unnecessary to feed into the context.
the files that are fed to the AI as context.
This includes ignoring entire folders.
And then, for the 'rules' under Cursor...
So, this is the rule, right?
This means that the rules for Cursor go in here.
And we'll put the agent's RTS in here.
Well, that's because it depends on which IDE you're using.
Or if you're using one of those Chinese-made IDEs,
And other stuff like 'work', 'code', 'body', and so on.
Or if you're using any of these other IDEs.
So, you just go ahead and create different folders.
So, how do you know which specific folders to create?
Actually, it's not about how I know this is the right project.
You'll see that what I actually need are just the folders in this specific area.
So, all I really need is this whole bunch of stuff right here.
I really only need this stack of stuff.
And at most, maybe these two down here as well.
As for everything else, that's all because I have specific needs for them.
And then, it just gradually grew and grew from there.
And once it's all set up,
And that's how it ended up with all this stuff.
So, up to this point,
So, does everyone get how to set up the project?
If you got all that, drop a '1' in the chat.